# Des Gouttes & Associés



## Arun Chandrasekharan

Partner, Attorney at Law Deputy Secretary of the Supervisory Board CDB Former Member of the Board of the Geneva Bar Association

## Languages

English, (Swiss-)German, French, Italian

#### **Contact Details**

T + 41 22 704 30 50

arun.chandrasekharan@desgouttes.ch

## **Expertise**

#### **Commercial and Contracts**

Arun Chandrasekharan primarily advises, negotiates, drafts and resolves disputes related to service contracts, such as mandate agreements, distribution agreements, joint venture agreements, licensing agreements, outsourcing agreements, manufacturing agreements, supply agreements, management agreements, employment agreements or general consulting contracts both in international and domestic relations.

#### **Corporate**

Arun Chandrasekharan assists clients on transactions concerning the sale of companies or assets (including real estate transactions), investment in companies, transfer of technologies. He advises, negotiates, drafts and resolves disputes pertaining to banking matters (loan agreements, asset management, trade finance, etc.), shareholders' agreements, share or asset purchase agreements, investment agreements, convertible loan agreements and related agreements.

With his own personal experience on Boards of Directors, Arun Chandrasekharan regularly handles issues of corporate law including corporate housekeeping and corporate restructuring.

#### Litigation and Arbitration

Arun Chandrasekharan is an expert in dispute resolutions both before courts in Geneva and other cantons as well as in arbitration and mediation. He regularly acts as sole arbitrator, party appointed arbitrator and mediator both in ad hoc proceedings as well as in institutional arbitrations (International Chamber of Commerce, Swiss Arbitration Center, Arbitral Tribunal of the Swiss Association of Asset Managers).

#### **Education**

2000	Admission to the Geneva Bar (ranked 2 <sup>nd</sup> best)
1998	University of Geneva, Licence en droit
1995	Mathematisch-Naturwissenschaftliches Gymnasium Rämibühl, Zurich, Matura

#### Career

#### **Law Firms**

Since 2002	Partner, Des Gouttes & Associés				
2001-2002	Associate	e, Des Go	uttes 8	Associés	
1998-2000	Trainee Associés	Lawyer,	Des	Gouttes	&

#### **Independent Board Memberships**

Since 2014	Member of the Board of Directors of Dynawealth Management Ltd.
Since 2010	Member of the Board of Directors of SI Domaine du Parc SA
2015-2021	Member of the Board of Directors of the Geneva Bar Association
2002-2004	Member of the Board of Directors of Imtix Sangstat (Switzerland) GmbH

### Other Activities

Since 2021	Deputy Secretary Board CDB	of th	ne Superv	isory
Since 2019	Vice-President Commission of Association			
Since 2018	Member of the Co		sion en m	atière

## Des Gouttes & Associés

## **Employment and Immigration**

Arun Chandrasekharan has a robust experience in the negotiation and drafting of employment agreements, bonus and incentive schemes, termination (individual or mass) agreements, and social plans. He furthermore represents both companies and employees in managerial positions in front of labor courts, in all industry sectors with a focus on the banking industry.

## **Memberships**

Geneva Bar Association (OdA), Swiss Bar Association (SAV), International Fraud Group